const QuizMockQuestions = [
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504f7",
    correctAnswer: "windmills, watermills and animal engines",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "the ecology of plant communities",
      "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension",
      "the biosphere and its relations to the lithosphere and atmosphere",
    ],
    question: "What is Molinology the study of?",
    tags: ["words", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "624334dfcfaae40c1296146f",
    correctAnswer: "An Owlet",
    incorrectAnswers: ["A Caterpillar", "A Codling", "A Colt"],
    question: "What would you call a baby owl?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950521",
    correctAnswer: "sacred texts",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "a variant of physiognomy",
      "relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees",
      "waves or wave motions",
    ],
    question: "What is Hierographology the study of?",
    tags: ["words", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "62433531cfaae40c1296148f",
    correctAnswer: "A Bull",
    incorrectAnswers: ["A Drone", "A Tiercel", "A Rooster"],
    question: "A male sea lion is known as what?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950fd9",
    correctAnswer: "Copper and Zinc",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Iron and Bronze", "Silver and Steel", "Tin and Gold"],
    question: "Which two metals make up brass?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950fe2",
    correctAnswer: "Hibiscus",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Orchid", "Lavender", "Rose"],
    question: "Which plant is known for attracting hummingbirds?",
    tags: ["biology", "animals", "plants", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "62443784746187c5e7be935a",
    correctAnswer: "Calcium carbonate",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Deuterium Oxide",
      "Calcium magnesium carbonate",
      "Sodium bicarbonate",
    ],
    question: "What chemical compound makes limestone?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "62433536cfaae40c12961491",
    correctAnswer: "A Pup",
    incorrectAnswers: ["A Foal", "A Calf", "A Piglet"],
    question: "A young sea lion is known as what?",
    tags: ["animals", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950542",
    correctAnswer: "the process of biological evolution",
    incorrectAnswers: ["the eyes", "crop circles", "butterflies and moths"],
    question: "What is Evolutionary biology the study of?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510ae",
    correctAnswer: "Oxygen",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Hydrogen", "Dark Matter", "Higgs Bosons"],
    question: "Of what is 98% of the weight of water made?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951026",
    correctAnswer: "Entomology",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Botany", "Zoology", "Horticulture"],
    question: "What Is The Study Of Insects Called? ",
    tags: ["words", "animals", "biology", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504b1",
    correctAnswer: "plankton",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "interactions among organisms and the water cycle",
      "the Islam",
      "society",
    ],
    question: "What is Planktology the study of?",
    tags: ["words", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f95051e",
    correctAnswer: "Japanese people",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "glaciers",
      "the effects of atmospheric conditions on living organisms",
      "fungi",
    ],
    question: "What is Japanology the study of?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95103d",
    correctAnswer: "Es",
    incorrectAnswers: ["El", "En", "Ei"],
    question: "What is the chemical symbol for einsteinium?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9505a4",
    correctAnswer: "Things which cannot be known",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Relationships between living organisms and their environment",
      "Nerves",
      "Algae",
    ],
    question: "What is Agnoiology the study of?",
    tags: ["science", "words"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950541",
    correctAnswer: "the process of human psychological evolution",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "eggs",
      "the study of picture postcards",
      "sacred texts",
    ],
    question: "What is Evolutionary psychology the study of?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951065",
    correctAnswer: "Liver",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Kidney", "Stomach", "Bladder"],
    question: "What does hepatitis affect?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950ff9",
    correctAnswer: "Kidney",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Liver", "Bladder", "Stomach"],
    question: "Which Organ's Action Is Replaced By Artifical Dialysis?",
    tags: ["medicine", "anatomy", "biology", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "6242cb5ed543524f1b19c927",
    correctAnswer: "A stud",
    incorrectAnswers: ["A cete", "A paddling", "A troop"],
    question: "What is the word for a group of mares?",
    tags: ["science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504de",
    correctAnswer: "dragonflies and damselflies",
    incorrectAnswers: ["wine", "myths", "race"],
    question: "What is Odonatology the study of?",
    tags: ["words", "science"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
  },
];

export { QuizMockQuestions };
